{
    "id": "6a7eaf15060440e18b64d6abf50111d7",
    "title": "Active Or Passive",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We .................................. this.",
            "description": "When the subject is the doer of the action, we use an active verb.",
            "answers": [
                "will not tolerate",
                "will not be tolerated",
                "will not be tolerating"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b342bbd22e154e899f2e80bdbc23d5ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ................................. responsible for the failure of the project.",
            "description": "We use a passive verb when the subject is not the doer of the action.",
            "answers": [
                "held",
                "was held"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "388fe24dcf174ab08f87c131e83d7cdb"
        },
        {
            "question": "The prizes .................................... by the chief guest.",
            "description": "We use a passive verb when the subject is not the doer of the action.",
            "answers": [
                "distributed",
                "were distributed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5e78e45e40ad452cb6b7211a01e37d7a"
        },
        {
            "question": "When mummy arrived, the problem .....................................",
            "description": "We use a passive verb when the subject is not the doer of the action.",
            "answers": [
                "resolved",
                "was resolved"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bc7260e506a0446e90ad6b88437c9930"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................... to him yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "talked",
                "was talked"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6452f493d3c04d6d85a1e7ba0f00acd3"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ..................................... of the developments.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have informed",
                "have been informed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "915adb8d8abd4cd0a5c889a14f46bff9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ...................................... his bride to his friends.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "introduced",
                "was introduced",
                "has been introduced"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "01f1759765fc4c9d90d7fc6e4ecde8da"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................... to a nice woman at the party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "introduced",
                "was introduced",
                "have introduced"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1161e93d32144de3be4d68d2e44ae1e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ..................................... for his kind deeds.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "still remembered",
                "is still remembered",
                "is still remembering"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3988d9bcc314473d8c59689601100cba"
        },
        {
            "question": "Everyone .................................. to hear the news.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shocked",
                "has shocked",
                "was shocked"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "25f45b640c294440b1dd10714d2172cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "We .......................................... anything from them yet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have not heard",
                "have not been heard",
                "have not been hearing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "85d6b5a6193840798dcd026fe889e620"
        },
        {
            "question": "The girl .................................... by a passerby.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saved",
                "was saved",
                "was saving"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4ed4e27c634e47e4a1ae48b4eb89dbaf"
        }
    ]
}